##### Search Suggestions Modal Dialog

Close  

Search Products

New [SHOP ALL New](https://www.venus.com/whats-new) [New Clothing](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=351~530~3377~) [New Swim & Cover-ups](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=351~530~3376~) Clothing [SHOP ALL Clothing](https://www.venus.com/clothing) [Best Sellers](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~8473~) [Dresses](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~72~) [Tops](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~63~) [Jumpsuits & Rompers](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~183~) [Sweaters](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~69~) [Jackets & Coats](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~73~) [Loungewear](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~164~) [All Bottoms](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~8201~) [Jeans](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~2999~) [Pants](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~70~) [Shorts](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~7614~) [Skirts](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~71~) [Shoes & Boots](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~75~) [Accessories & Handbags](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~77~) [Jewelry](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~3599~) [Matching Sets](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~8324~) [Work Wardrobe](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~8107~) [Anything But Basics](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~7045~) [Size Chart](https://www.venus.com/size-info) [Dress Fit Guide](https://www.venus.com/fit-guide/dresses) [Sale](https://www.venus.com/sale) [Clearance](https://www.venus.com/clearance) Dresses [SHOP ALL Dresses](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~72~) [Sundresses & Day Dresses](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~72~7613~) [Maxi Dresses](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~72~4080~) [Midi Dresses](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~72~7388~) [Short Dresses](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~72~7389~) [Cocktail Dresses](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~72~5031~) [Sweater Dresses](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~72~4214~) Swim [SHOP ALL Swim](https://www.venus.com/swimwear) [Shop By Print/Color](https://www.venus.com/shopbyfabric.aspx) [Shop By Style](https://www.venus.com/style/swim) [Cheeky Bottoms](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=24~93~) [Moderate Bottoms](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=24~95~) [Full Bottoms](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=24~96~) [Best of Swim](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=24~8508~) [Shop All Bottoms](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=24~5977~) [One-Piece Swimsuits & Swim Dresses](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=24~97~) [Cover-ups](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=24~98~) [Sustainable Swimwear](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=24~7559~) [Size Chart](https://www.venus.com/size-info) [Fit Guide](https://www.venus.com/fit-guide/swimwear) [Sale](https://www.venus.com/style/swim-sale) [Clearance](https://www.venus.com/style/swim-clearance) Lingerie [SHOP ALL Lingerie](https://www.venus.com/lingerie) [Pearl by Venus®](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=129~7602~) [Bras](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=129~5334~) [Panties](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=129~5335~) [Pajamas & Sleepwear](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=129~6923~) [Sexy Lingerie](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=129~4042~) [Shapewear & Solutions](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=129~4043~) [Lingerie Fit Guide](https://www.venus.com/fit-guide/lingerie) [Sale](https://www.venus.com/style/lingerie-sale) [Clearance](https://www.venus.com/style/lingerie-clearance) Plus [SHOP ALL Plus](https://www.venus.com/plus-size-clothing) [Clothing](https://www.venus.com/plus-size-clothing) [Shoes & Boots](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~75~) [Accessories & Handbags](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~77~) [Jewelry](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=7~3599~) [Swim](https://www.venus.com/plus-size-swimwear) [Sale](https://www.venus.com/style/clothing-plus-size-sale) [Clearance](https://www.venus.com/style/clothing-plus-size-clearance) Trends [SHOP ALL Trends](https://www.venus.com/trends) [Tropic Bohème](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=351~515~8580~) [Americana](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=351~515~5832~) [Salsa Sunsets](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=351~515~8539~) [Under the Sun](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=351~515~8483~) [La Dolce Vita](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=351~515~8481~) [The Denim Shop](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=351~515~7586~) [Ticket to Paradise](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=351~515~8458~) [Best Dressed Guest](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=351~515~7956~) [Fresh Florals](https://www.venus.com/products.aspx?BRANCH=351~515~8253~) Pre-Order [SHOP ALL Pre-Order](https://www.venus.com/pre-order) [Clothing](https://www.venus.com/style/clothing-pre-order) Sale [SHOP ALL Sale](https://www.venus.com/sale) [Clothing Sale](https://www.venus.com/style/clothing-sale) [Clothing Clearance](https://www.venus.com/style/clothing-clearance) [Swim Sale](https://www.venus.com/style/swim-sale) [Swim Clearance](https://www.venus.com/style/swim-clearance) [Lingerie Sale](https://www.venus.com/style/lingerie-sale) [Lingerie Clearance](https://www.venus.com/style/lingerie-clearance) [Plus Size Clothing Sale](https://www.venus.com/style/clothing-plus-size-sale) [Plus Size Clothing Clearance](https://www.venus.com/style/clothing-plus-size-clearance) [Plus Size Swim Sale](https://www.venus.com/style/swim-plus-size-sale) [Plus Size Swim Clearance](https://www.venus.com/style/swim-plus-size-clearance)

Search Products

* New
* Clothing

* Dresses
        
* Swim

* Lingerie

* Plus

* Trends
        
* Pre-Order
* Sale

Venus Privacy Policy
====================

Venus respects your privacy and the security of your personal information. For this reason, we have updated our Privacy Policy (“Policy”) as of April 1, 2023. It describes the information that we collect, how we use it and what choices you have. This Policy applies when you access our websites and mobile applications, contact us by phone, email, and chat or connect with us in any other manner, including in our social media, APP and SMS channels. We may change or add to this privacy policy, so we encourage you to review it periodically. For our terms of use for our website, please click [here.](https://www.venus.com/terms-of-use).

Contents

* * *

[What information is collected?](#pp-info-collected) [Do Not Sell My Personal Info](#pp-donotsellheading-div) [Third-party automated collection and interest-based advertising](#pp-third-party) [How is your information used?](#pp-info-used) [How is your information shared?](#pp-info-shared) [What choices do you have?](#pp-choices) [How is your personal information protected?](#pp-info-protected) [State Privacy Laws](#ccpa)

Types of information we collect may include:

* * *

* Name
* Mailing address
* Email address
* Phone (or mobile) number
* Date of birth or age
* Credit/debit card number
* Purchase/return/exchange information
* Registry or list information
* Loyalty account information
* Your mobile device information (e.g., device model, operating system version, device date and time, unique device identifiers, mobile network information)
* How you use our sites and mobile applications, search terms, pages you visit on our mobile applications and application performance, as discussed further below
* Geo-location and in-store location

DO NOT SELL MY PERSONAL INFO

* * *

Certain state laws governing your privacy rights, including the California Privacy Rights Act (CPRA) and the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act (VCDPA), provide you with certain rights regarding your personal information. This section describes those state privacy rights and how to exercise them.

If you have any questions about this Notice, would like to exercise your rights under the state privacy laws, or would like to request that we do not sell your information, please contact our Customer Care department:

* Via email at [privacy@venus.com](mailto:privacy@venus.com)
* By phone at 1-888-782-2224
* By Mail to:  
    Venus Fashion, Inc.  
    Attention Customer Care-Privacy  
    11711 Marco Beach Drive  
    Jacksonville, FL 32224

Automated Information Collection

We may collect information collected automatically with information we already have about you in order to identify you as a Venus guest, and to improve your experience. If we are able to identify you as a Venus guest we may, for example, link your activity on our website to your activity on one of our mobile applications. This allows us to provide you with a personalized experience regardless of how you interact with us – online, mobile, on phone, etc.

In order to provide the best guest experience possible, we also use automated information collection technologies for reporting and analysis purposes. We examine metrics such as how users are shop on our website, on our mobile applications, and on our phone system, the performance of our marketing efforts, and your response to those marketing efforts.

Venus Automated Collection

We and our service providers use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us or third parties that use our services. This information helps us recognize repeat users, customize their website experience, store items in their cart between visits and make our marketing messages more relevant. Examples of this information include but are not limited to pages you visit, ads you click on, type of browser/device/hardware, purchase information, IP based geographic location and search terms. These technologies also enable us to prevent fraud or other harmful activities.

We may also allow third-party companies to place tags on our digital properties. The tags may collect information from cookies placed by other third-party companies. Our Privacy Policy does not cover these third-party companies. Please contact these third party companies directly for more information about their privacy policy and your choices regarding the tags and the information collected by the tags.

Cross-Context and Cross-Device Identification, Advertising, Personalization, and Advertising Attribution

Cross-Context

We may merge data collected from our own websites and mobile apps. Examples of the data collected by us or by third party companies include: cookie IDs, device Advertising IDs; transactions and browsing history; your interaction with our online and mobile advertisements, including advertisements we serve within our emails; information about ads we serve, such as which ad was served, your interactions with the ads, and the URLs where the ads are served from marketing partners such as Google; the email address we have on file for you; any Registry information you have provided us; demographic and other information regarding your likely commercial interests from third parties; and telephone transaction data. This combination of data enables us to see users’ and Guests’ web activity on Venus websites, app activity on Venus apps, and interactions with our online and mobile advertisements, to create a single set of information from all of the various contexts with which we or our partners interact with you, and to understand how well Venus’s advertisements perform in terms of translating to transactions online, in app, and on Venus’s phones. It also helps us improve our users’ and Guests’ experience by delivering more personalized advertising, including email advertising, social media advertising, and paid search advertising, and helps us create more personalized online and in-app experiences.

Cross-Device

We may also link your various devices so that content you see on one device can result in relevant advertising on another device. This allows us to deliver more relevant and consistent advertising to you (for example, if you purchase a product on our website using your desktop, we are able to avoid showing you an advertisement on the same product on your tablet. Instead, we may show you an ad on your tablet for complimentary products to the one you just purchased on our website). We also measure the performance of such ads and deliver information on advertising performance to our advertising partners in aggregate form.

The help function of your browser should contain instructions on how to set your computer to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued or to not receive cookies at any time. If you set your device to not receive cookies at any time, certain personalized services cannot be provided to you, and accordingly, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our features.

How Is Your Information Used?

* * *

Examples of how we use the information we collect include:

Product and Service Fulfillment

* Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, and returns/exchanges
* Respond to requests for information about our products and services in our catalogs, on our websites or mobile applications, or to otherwise serve you
* Connect with you regarding guest service via our customer care center or on social media or internet chat platforms or via text messages.
* Provide services such as a Wishlist that the consumer can choose to share.
* Fulfill benefits associated with use of our services, such as award and redeem points through our loyalty programs, etc.
* Administer sweepstakes and contests
* Allow you to, using our mobile applications: sign up for promotions and offers, search for products and check availability, check prices, provide product ratings and reviews, track your orders, scan a UPC barcode or QR code Our Purposes (including but not limited to marketing)
* Deliver catalogs, promotions, offers, newsletters, emails, mobile messages, and social media notifications
* Provide interactive features of the website or mobile applications, such as product reviews or daily/weekly promos, send marketing communications and other information regarding products, services and promotions
* Administer promotions, surveys, and focus groups

Third-Party Automated Collection and Interest-Based Advertising

* * *

Venus participates in interest-based advertising (IBA), also known as Online Behavioral Advertising. We use third-party advertising companies to display ads tailored to your individual interests based on how you browse and shop online, as well as to provide advertising-related services such as ad delivery, reporting, attribution, analytics, and market research. Venus adheres to the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) self-regulatory principles for IBA. To learn more about IBA or to opt-out of this type of advertising, visit the [Network Advertising Initiative website](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance website](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN). Options you select are browser- and device-specific.

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our websites or use our mobile applications. This information is used to serve ads for Venus products or services when you visit our websites. These companies use non-personally-identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, hardware/software information, cookie and session ID) and personally identifiable information (e.g., static IP address) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you or advertising-related services, such as ad delivery, reporting, attribution, analytics, and market research. These parties typically use a cookie, web beacon or other similar tracking technologies to collect this information.

Our Do Not Track Policy

Some browsers have a “do not track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. At this time, we do not respond to browser “do not track” signals, but we do provide you the option to opt out of interest-based advertising.

Mobile Location Information

If you use a mobile device, your device may share location information (when you enable location services) with our websites, mobile applications, services, or our service providers. We use this information to improve our services, and provide you more relevant and personalized advertisements, services, and promotions. To manage how you share your device’s location settings, go to the Choices section of this privacy policy.

User Experience Information

In order to improve guest online and mobile shopping experiences, help with fraud identification, and assist our guest relations representatives in resolving issues guests may experience in completing online purchases, we use tools to monitor certain user experience information; including login information, IP address, data regarding pages visited and ads clicked, specific actions taken on pages visited (e.g. information entered during checkout process), browser and device information.

Social Media

Venus engages with guests on multiple social media platforms (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, and Pinterest). If you contact us on one of our social media platforms, request guest service via social media, or otherwise direct us to communicate with you via social media, we may contact you via direct message or use other social media tools to interact with you. In these instances, your interactions with us are governed by this privacy policy as well as the privacy policy of the social media platform you use.

Social Media Widgets

Our sites and mobile applications include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, Google Plus, Pinterest, and Twitter widgets. These features may collect information about you such as your IP address and which page you are visiting on our site. They may set a cookie or employ other tracking technologies to accomplish this. Social media features and widgets may be hosted by a third party. Your interactions with those features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.

Social Media Ads

We may display Venus ads to you through social media platforms. These ads are sent to groups of people who share traits such as likely commercial interests and demographics. For example, we may have Venus guests who have expressed an interest in shopping for clothing, swimwear, shoes, etc. See the policies of each social media platform for additional information about these types of ads.

Information from Other Sources

We may collect data that is publicly available online. For example, information you submit in a public forum (e.g., a blog, chat room, or social network) may be used to personalize your experience. You are responsible for the information you choose to post online.

We also obtain information provided by third parties. For instance, we obtain demographic and other information from companies that can enhance our existing guest information to improve the accuracy and add to the information we have about our guests (e.g., adding address information).

This improves our ability to contact you and increases the relevance of our marketing by providing better product recommendations or special offers that may interest you.

Internal Operations

* Improve the effectiveness of our website, mobile experience, customer care experience, products, services, and marketing efforts
* Conduct research and analysis, including focus groups and surveys
* Perform other business activities as needed, or as described elsewhere in this policy

Prevention of Fraud and Other Harm

* Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft and otherwise protect our guests and our business

Legal Compliance

* For example, assist law enforcement and respond to legal/regulatory inquiries

How Is Your Information Shared?

* * *

Venus Subsidiaries and Affiliates

We share the information we collect within Venus Fashion, Inc., which includes all Venus subsidiaries and affiliates. Venus Fashion, Inc. may use this information to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you.

Venus Fashion, Inc. owns and operates Venus websites, mobile applications, and issues the Venus Credit Card through Comenity Bank. Venus Fashion, Inc. subsidiaries and affiliates include, but are not limited to CreationL, Inc. and Lascana Fashion, Inc.

Card Issuing Bank

We may share the information we collect with our banking partner, Comenity Bank that issues the Venus Credit Card.

Service Providers

We may share the information we collect with companies that provide support services to us (such as printers, email providers, mobile marketing services, analytics providers, web hosting providers, call center/chat providers, sweepstakes vendors, payment processors, data enhancement services, fraud prevention providers or shipping services providers, including product vendors) or that help us market our products and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions.

Legal Requirements

We may disclose information we collect when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law; to enforce or apply applicable terms and conditions and other agreements; to facilitate the financing, securitization, insuring, sale, assignment, bankruptcy, or disposal of all or part of our business or assets; or to protect the rights property or safety of our company, our guests or others.

Elsewhere at Your Direction

At your direction or request, or when you otherwise consent, we may share your information.

Sharing with Other Companies (for their marketing purposes)

We may share your personal information with other companies, or organizations that are not part of Venus. These companies and organizations may use the information we share to provide special offers and opportunities to you. To opt-out of our sharing of your personal information with such companies and organizations, click [here](https://www.venus.com/contact).

Sharing Non-identifiable or Aggregate Information with Third Parties

We may share non-identifiable or aggregate information with third parties for lawful purposes.

Business Transfers

In connection with the sale or transfer of some or all of our business assets, we may transfer the corresponding information regarding our guests. We also may retain a copy of that guest information.

What Choices Do You Have?

* * *

Do Not Sell My Personal Info

Certain state laws governing your privacy rights, including the California Privacy Rights Act (CPRA) and the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act (VCDPA), provide you with certain rights regarding your personal information. This section describes those state privacy rights and how to exercise them.

If you have any questions about this Notice, would like to exercise your rights under the state privacy laws, or would like to request that we do not sell your information, please contact our Customer Care department:

* Via email at [privacy@venus.com](mailto:privacy@venus.com)
* By phone at 1-888-782-2224
* By Mail to:  
    Venus Fashion, Inc.  
    Attention Customer Care-Privacy  
    11711 Marco Beach Drive  
    Jacksonville, FL 32224

* * *

Postal Mail

If you do not wish to receive catalogs, coupons, and other promotional postal mail, click [here](https://www.venus.com/contact).

Telephone

If you do not wish to receive promotional telephone calls, click [here](https://www.venus.com/contact).

Email

If you do not wish to receive promotional emails from us, click [here](https://www.venus.com/contact). You also have the ability to unsubscribe from promotional emails via the unsubscribe link included in each promotional email.

Mobile

Text Messages

We may send text messages you have consented to receive.

You can cancel text messages at any time by texting the word "STOP" to 39512. After you send "STOP", we may send you an additional text message to confirm that you have been unsubscribed. You will no longer receive text messages from that short code, but you may receive marketing messages if you are subscribed to other lists (e.g., email).

If at any time you have questions about the text messages, text the word "HELP" to 39512. After you send "HELP" we will respond with instructions on how to cancel text messages and provide a point of contact for our SMS text message provider.

You may also reach us at [email@venus.com](mailto:email@venus.com) or 1-888-782-2224.

By joining via text, you consent and agree to receive recurring automated marketing messages from VENUS at the cell number used to send the join text. Consent is not a condition of any purchase. Message and data rates may apply.

Browser Notifications

You may opt-out from allowing Venus to send you browser notifications by adjusting the permissions in your internet browser. Please refer to your specific browser for instructions on how to adjust the privacy and security settings.

Push Notifications

You may opt-out from allowing Venus to send you push notifications by adjusting the permissions in your mobile device. This opt does not apply to in app notifications.

Geo-Location

You may prevent your mobile device from sharing your location data by adjusting the permissions on your mobile device or within the relevant app.

Uninstall a Venus Mobile Application

You can stop all further collection of information by a Venus mobile application by uninstalling the Venus mobile application. You may use the standard uninstall process available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network.

Note: If you uninstall the mobile application from your device, the Venus unique identifier associated with your device will continue to be stored. If you re-install the application on the same device, Venus will be able to re-associate this identifier to your previous transactions and activities.

Sharing with Other Companies (for their marketing purposes)

If you do not wish us to share the personal information we have collected with other unaffiliated companies (for their marketing purposes), click [here](https://www.venus.com/contact).

OTHER WEB SITE ANALYTICS SERVICES

Analytics services including Google Analytics provide services that analyze information regarding visits to our websites and mobile applications. They use cookies, web beacons, and other tracking mechanisms to collect this information.

* To learn more about Google’s privacy practices, click [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites).
* To learn more about Salesforce’s privacy practices or to opt-out of cookies set to facilitate reporting, click [here](https://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/).
* To learn more about Attentive's privacy practices or to opt out of cookies set to facilitate reporting, click [here](https://www.attentive.com/privacy).

How Is Your Personal Information Protected?

* * *

Security Methods

We maintain administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to protect your personal information. When we collect or transmit sensitive information such as a credit or debit card number, we use industry standard methods to protect that information. However, no e-commerce solution, website, mobile application, database or system is completely secure or “hacker proof.” You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse.

Children’s Personal Information

We recognize the particular importance of protecting privacy where children are involved. We do not knowingly collect personal information online from children under the age of 16. No one under age 16 may provide any personal information on the website. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on this website. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.

Venus Privacy Policy Scope

* * *

This privacy policy applies to all current or former guest personal information, except for information collected by or provided in connection with:

* A Venus Credit Card. See the [Venus Credit Card Privacy Policy](https://d.comenity.net/venus/common/privacy/PrivacyLanding.xhtml). Note, contact information you provide on a Venus Credit Card application is provided to both Comenity Bank and to Venus.
* Completing an application for employment with Venus.

Our website may offer links to other sites. If you visit one of these sites, you may want to review the privacy policy on that site. In addition, you may have visited our website through a link or a banner advertisement on another site. In such cases, the site you linked from may collect information from people who click on the banner or link. You may want to refer to the privacy policies on those sites to see how they collect and use this information.

STATE PRIVACY RIGHTS

* * *

Certain states have specific laws that provide you with rights regarding your personal information, including but not necessarily limited to the California Privacy Rights Act and the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act.

If you have any questions about this Notice or to exercise your rights under your state’s privacy laws, please contact our Customer Care department:

* Via email at [privacy@venus.com](mailto:privacy@venus.com)
* By phone at 1-888-782-2224
* By Mail to:  
    Venus Fashion, Inc.  
    Attention Customer Care-Privacy 11711 Marco Beach Drive  
    Jacksonville, FL 32224

Information We Collect and How It Is Used

We collect information from you in several different ways on this site with the goal of improving your customer experience with Venus. During the past twelve months, we have collected the following types of information:

**_Identifiers_** such as a real names, aliases, postal addresses, unique personal identifiers, online identifiers, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, email addresses, or other similar identifiers;

_Collected from:_ Information you provide to us, or we collect when you use our services or website.

_Business use:_

* Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, and returns/exchanges
* Respond to requests for information about our products and services in our catalogs, on our websites or mobile applications, or to otherwise serve you
* Connect with you regarding guest service via our customer care center or on social media or internet chat platforms or via text messages
* Provide services such as a Wishlist that you can choose to share
* Fulfill benefits associated with use of our services, such as award and redemption points through our loyalty programs, etc.
* Administer sweepstakes and contests
* Allow you to, using our mobile applications: sign up for promotions and offers, search for products and check availability, check prices, provide product ratings and reviews, and track your orders
* Deliver catalogs, promotions, offers, newsletters, emails, mobile messages, and social media notifications
* Provide interactive features of the website or mobile applications, such as product reviews or daily/weekly promos, send marketing communications and other information regarding products, services and promotions
* Administer promotions, surveys, and focus groups
* Improve the effectiveness of our website, mobile experience, customer care experience, products, services, and marketing efforts
* Conduct research and analysis, including focus groups and surveys
* Perform other business activities as needed, or as described elsewhere in this policy
* Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft and otherwise protect our guests and our business
* Legal compliance—for example, to assist law enforcement or respond to legal/regulatory inquiries

**_Categories of personal information_** such as telephone numbers, credit card numbers, debit card numbers, and other financial information;

_Collected from:_ Information you provide to us, or we collect when you use our services or website.

_Business use:_

* Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, and returns/exchanges
* Fulfill benefits associated with use of our services, such as award and redemption points through our loyalty programs, etc.
* Administer sweepstakes and contests
* Perform other business activities as needed, or as described elsewhere in this policy
* Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft and otherwise protect our guests and our business
* Legal compliance—for example, to assist law enforcement or respond to legal/regulatory inquiries

**_Internet or other electronic network activity information,_** including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer's interaction with an Internet Web site, application, or advertisement;

_Collected from:_ Information we collect when you use our services or website.

_Business use:_

* Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, and returns/exchanges
* Connect with you regarding guest service via our customer care center or on social media or internet chat platforms or via text messages.
* Fulfill benefits associated with use of our services, such as award and redemption points through our loyalty programs, etc.
* Allow you to, using our mobile applications: sign up for promotions and offers, search for products and check availability, check prices, provide product ratings and reviews, and track your orders
* Deliver catalogs, promotions, offers, newsletters, emails, mobile messages, and social media notifications
* Provide interactive features of the website or mobile applications, such as product reviews or daily/weekly promos, send marketing communications and other information regarding products, services and promotions
* Administer promotions, surveys, and focus groups
* Improve the effectiveness of our website, mobile experience, customer care experience, products, services, and marketing efforts
* Conduct research and analysis, including focus groups and surveys
* Perform other business activities as needed, or as described elsewhere in this policy
* Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft and otherwise protect our guests and our business
* Legal compliance—for example, to assist law enforcement or respond to legal/regulatory inquiries

**_Commercial information,_** including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies;

_Collected from:_ Information you provide to us, or we collect when you use our services or website.

_Business use:_

* Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, and returns/exchanges
* Respond to requests for information about our products and services in our catalogs, on our websites or mobile applications, or to otherwise serve you
* Connect with you regarding guest service via our customer care center or on social media or internet chat platforms or via text messages
* Provide services such as a Wishlist that you can choose to share
* Fulfill benefits associated with use of our services, such as award and redemption points through our loyalty programs, etc.
* Administer sweepstakes and contests
* Allow you to, using our mobile applications: sign up for promotions and offers, search for products and check availability, check prices, provide product ratings and reviews, and track your orders
* Deliver catalogs, promotions, offers, newsletters, emails, mobile messages, and social media notifications
* Provide interactive features of the website or mobile applications, such as product reviews or daily/weekly promos, send marketing communications and other information regarding products, services and promotions
* Administer promotions, surveys, and focus groups
* Improve the effectiveness of our website, mobile experience, customer care experience, products, services, and marketing efforts
* Conduct research and analysis, including focus groups and surveys
* Perform other business activities as needed, or as described elsewhere in this policy
* Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft and otherwise protect our guests and our business
* Legal compliance—for example, to assist law enforcement or respond to legal/regulatory inquiries

**_Geolocation data_**

_Collected from:_ Information we collect when you use our services or website; information provided by third parties.

_Business use:_

* Allow you to, using our mobile applications: sign up for promotions and offers, search for products and check availability, check prices, provide product ratings and reviews, and track your orders
* Provide interactive features of the website or mobile applications, such as product reviews or daily/weekly promos, send marketing communications and other information regarding products, services and promotions
* Improve the effectiveness of our website, mobile experience, customer care experience, products, services, and marketing efforts
* Conduct research and analysis, including focus groups and surveys
* Perform other business activities as needed, or as described elsewhere in this policy
* Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft and otherwise protect our guests and our business
* Legal compliance—for example, to assist law enforcement or respond to legal/regulatory inquiries

**_Inferences,_** system-generated predictions about your interests and preferences

_Collected from:_ Created internally

_Business use:_

* Respond to requests for information about our products and services in our catalogs, on our websites or mobile applications, or to otherwise serve you
* Fulfill benefits associated with use of our services, such as award and redemption points through our loyalty programs, etc.
* Deliver catalogs, promotions, offers, newsletters, emails, mobile messages, and social media notifications
* Improve the effectiveness of our website, mobile experience, customer care experience, products, services, and marketing efforts
* Perform other business activities as needed, or as described elsewhere in this policy
* Legal compliance—for example, to assist law enforcement or respond to legal/regulatory inquiries

How Information May Be Shared

During the past twelve months, we have shared the following information for business purposes. Please note that for purposes of this notice, personal information does not include deidentified, aggregated, or anonymized information that is maintained in a form that is not capable of being associated with or linked to you.

Sale for a Business Purpose:

We do not sell your personal information for any monetary consideration. However, under some circumstances a transfer of personal information to a third party without monetary consideration may still be considered a “sale” under certain state’s laws. If you purchase from us, Venus may opt your name, address, email address and order information into a cooperative marketing database used by other companies that may want to market goods or services to you.

If you wish to opt-out of the sale of personal information, please email us at [privacy@venus.com](mailto:privacy@venus.com) or you may mail or telephone us using the contact addresses and toll-free telephone number listed above. You may authorize another to submit a request to opt-out on your behalf, but only if you provide the authorized agent with signed, written permission to do so. So as to ensure your privacy, we reserve the right to deny a request from an authorized agent who does not submit proof that they have been authorized to act on your behalf. If exercised, the decision to opt-out will be valid for twelve months, at which time we may request that you authorize the sale of personal information again.

Disclosure for a Business Purpose:

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Third Party | Purpose | Category of Personal Information |
| Operating system & platform | Calculation of sales tax | Identifiers: Customer address<br><br>  <br>Commercial information: Order information |
| Operating system & platform | Address validation and correction | Identifiers: Customer address |
| Operating system & platform | Credit card processing | Identifiers: Name and customer billing address, telephone, email address<br><br>  <br>Commercial information: Order information<br><br>  <br>Personal information: Credit card information |
| Operating system & platform | Private Label Credit Card<br><br>Prescreen and credit check by Comenity Bank to issue Venus Credit Card | Identifiers: Name and customer billing address, telephone, email, encrypted credit card information<br><br>  <br>Commercial information: Order information<br><br>  <br>Personal information for credit check by bank: Birthdate, social security number, annual income (Comenity collects and stores; Venus does not store or use this information.) See the [Venus Credit Card Privacy Policy.](https://d.comenity.net/venus/common/privacy/PrivacyLanding.xhtml) |
| Operating system & platform<br><br>Data analytics providers | Fraud detection | Identifiers: Name and customer billing address, telephone, email<br><br>  <br>Commercial information: Order information, customer account history<br><br>  <br>Personal information: Venus.com browsing history |
| Operating system & platform | Email marketing | Identifiers: Name and customer email address, birth month and year<br><br>  <br>Commercial information: Order information<br><br>  <br>Internet information: Venus.com browsing history |
| Operating system & platform | Transactional emails (order confirmations, password resets, etc.) and order management & fulfillment | Identifiers: Name; bill-to and ship-to addresses, email address and telephone number<br><br>  <br>Commercial information: Order information |
| Operating system & platform<br><br>  <br>Drop ship vendors | Shipping | Identifiers: Name and customer address<br><br>  <br>Commercial information: Order information |
| Operating system & platform | Customer support | Identifiers: Customer name, email, address, telephone number<br><br>  <br>Commercial information: Order information; mailing list statuses |
| Data analytics providers | Website analytics/improving our products and services | Internet information: Venus.com Browsing history; device info, op system, version, browser, etc.<br><br>  <br>Commercial information: Order information<br><br>  <br>Identifiers: IP address; Device and Account ID if signed into Venus<br><br>  <br>Inferences: System-generated predictions about your interests and preferences |
| Social networks<br><br>  <br>Advertising networks<br><br>  <br>Data analytics providers<br><br>  <br>Operating system & platform | Online advertising and product recommendations | Internet information: Venus.com browsing history and browser information<br><br>  <br>Identifiers: IP address; email address; unique personal identifiers such as device ID and Venus Account ID<br><br>  <br>Geolocation data<br><br>  <br>Commercial information: Order information |
| Data warehouse infrastructure service providers | Technical support and consulting for data warehouse infrastructure; business consulting regarding data driven marketing | Identifiers: Name, bill-to and ship-to addresses, customer email address, birth month and year, IP address; Device and Account ID if signed into Venus<br><br>  <br>Identifiers: IP address; email address; unique personal identifiers such as device ID and Venus Account ID<br><br>  <br>Internet information: Venus.com browsing history; device info, operating system, version, browser, etc., email/SMS sends and response<br><br>  <br>Commercial information: Order information, mailing list statuses |

Exercise of Your Data Rights

* You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information. Once we receive and verify your identity, we will disclose to you upon your request:
    * The categories of personal information we collected about you
    * The categories of sources from which the personal information has been collected
    * The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you
    * Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling any personal information
    * The categories of personal information about you that were sold or disclosed for a business purpose by category or categories of personal information for each category of third parties to whom the personal information was sold
* You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and verify your identity, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies.
    * We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service providers to:
        * Complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform our agreement with you.
        * Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities.
        * Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
        * Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise their free speech rights, or exercise another right provided for by law.
        * Comply with any relevant state or federal laws.
        * Enable internal uses that are reasonably aligned with consumer expectations based on your relationship with us.
        * Comply with a legal obligation.
        * Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.

To exercise the rights described above, please submit a verifiable request to us by clicking the following [privacy@venus.com](mailto:privacy@venus.com) to contact us by email or mail or telephone using the contact addresses and toll-free telephone number listed above.

Only you or a person whom you authorize to act on your behalf may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. If you wish to authorize another to act on your behalf, please be advised that we may require that you provide the authorized agent with signed written permission to submit a request and verify your own identity and confirm your permission directly with us, unless the authorized agent has a power of attorney. However, you may also make a verifiable consumer request on behalf of your minor child.

Our verification process works as follows. Before we may process a request, in order to protect your privacy, we will ask for you to confirm a few pieces of information that we have on our records about you, for example:

* Your address
* Your zip code
* Your email address
* Your phone number
* Your most recent purchase order number

If you make a request online to delete your personal information, we may need to confirm your request before we delete your information.

You may make a verifiable consumer request up to two times within a twelve-month period, without charge. Unfortunately, we cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm that the personal information relates to you. Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us. We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.

We try to respond to a verifiable consumer request within 45 days of its receipt. If we require more time, we will inform you of the reason and extension time period (up to 90 days). If you have an account with us, we will deliver our response to that account. If you do not have an account with us, we will deliver our response by mail or electronically, at your option. The response we provide will also explain any reasons we cannot comply with a request, if applicable.

We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your state law privacy rights.

Unless permitted by the state law privacy laws, we will not:

* Deny you goods or services.
* Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
* Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.
* Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.
